9xhost.info 2017-05-31

# 9xhost - Privacy Policy

## The Privacy policy below describes how 9xhost (the Company) collects and uses information about its customers and website visitors (The Users)

####  What information is collected from the User by the Company? 

Different types of personally identifiable information are collected from the user by the Company in order for the company to be able to provide its services. These includes, but is not limited to: name, mailing address, telephone numbers, email addresses, credit card information and other information that may be needed for providing the services requested by the User. All this information is provided voluntarily by the User through various order forms, email messages sent to the Company, submit forms, identification forms of LiveChat, information provided by the telephone etc. 

The Company also collects different types of non-personally identifiable information about its website visitors. These include but are not limited to referral URL's, Users' IP addresses, Users' use of website, information about the browsers used by the User, etc. Some of this information is collected through Cookies, which are small pieces of data that are sent to your browser from a web server and are stored on your computer's hard drive and help the Company identify the User. The user has the choice to modify his/her browser and thus to reject the Company's cookies.

#### How does the Company use the collected User's information?

The company uses the collected User's information mainly to provide the service requested by the User. It is used for initial service provision and ongoing User's support. The information can also be used by the Company for sending periodic emails announcing important service changes, new features, technical issue updates and news, different promotions etc. The Users may decide NOT to receive such emails by replying to any of them with "Unsubscribe" in the subject. The information is also used for improving the Company's effectiveness. Based on the data collected the company tries to improve its advertising and sales efforts, website layout and content and to make the overall experience of the User more rewarding. The information can also be used for resolving ownership and other disputes and enforcing agreements between the Company and the User.

#### Does the company disclose User's information to third parties?

Company take your privacy seriously and will take all measures to protect your personal information. Any personal information received will only be used to fill your order. Company will not sell or redistribute your information to anyone.
